ELIZABETH ARYSLANOVA

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

C.

+995 591 923 164

 \vee

e.aryslanova@gmail.com

in

/elizabeth-aryslanova



LizAryslanova.github.io



github.com/LizAryslanova



Batumi, Georgia

SUMMARY

Freelance machine learning engineer with a master's degree in optics and a background in mathematical modeling. With 15 years of dedicated mathematics teaching experience and a successful track record in online course production and consulting on 20+ projects.

EDUCATION

POSTGRADUATE DEGREE (Unfinished)

Mathematical Modeling, Numerical Methods and Software Solutions ITMO University 2014 - 2018

MASTER OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Photonics and Optical Information Technology ITMO University 2012 - 2014

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Photonics and Optical Information Technology ITMO University 2008 - 2012

SKILLS

Programming & Frameworks

Python, PyTorch, Librosa, NumPy, SciPy, Matplotlib, HTML, CSS

Software

Logic Pro X, Wolfram Mathematica , Final Cut, DaVinci Resolve, Affinity Photo, Affinity Designer,

Other

Capturing visuals, Public speaking, Teaching, Simplifying complexity, Soldering, Audio recording

LANGUAGES

English, Russian - Native German - Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

Freelance

Remote | Feb 2024 - Present

- Worked on 5 audio plugins.
- Implemented Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Temporal Convolutional Networks (TCNs) for audio-related machine learning models.
- · Prototyped DSP algorithms in Python.

MATHEMATICS SCIENCE TUTOR

Self Employed

Remote | Jan 2020 - Present St. Petersburg, Russia | Feb 2009 - Jan 2020

- Teaching mathematics, physics, and computer science to over 70 people ranging from 1st-grade pupils to master degree students from Russia, Israel, Germany, and the UK.
- Created and produced a <u>YouTube channel</u> about school mathematics (in Russian) that has over 120 videos, over 50k subscribers, and over 4M views.

RESEARCH ENGINEER

ITMO University

St. Petersburg, Russia | Mar 2011 - Jun 2017

- Mathematical modeling in physical electrochemistry.
- Oversaw grant administration for multiple projects, particularly in the field of quantum technologies.
- Taught a Bachelor's level course in Numerical methods in programming.
- Over <u>13 publications</u> in international journals.
- Over 20 conference presentations.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

DeepLearning.Al June 2023 - <u>coursera.org</u> Grade: 97.5 % <u>Certificate link</u> Winner of YouTube NextUp 2021 YouTube, Google Mar 2021 - <u>Channel link</u> Announcement link Specialist Certificate in General Music Studies Berklee Online Dec 2014 - <u>online.berklee.edu</u> Voice Technique, Music Foundations, Jazz Singing